careerbless.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy

* **Overview**

At www.careerbless.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information which is received and collected by www.careerbless.com and how it is used. The personal information which is submitted while registering to the site, will not be distributed or shared with any third-parties. We only use this data for our information, for research, to improve our services and for contacting you. www.careerbless.com is an open portal, so registering into site is not mandatory and also we won't verify your email address. Registration into the site is purely of user's interest. www.careerbless.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time and all such changes will be published in this site. 

* **Log Files**

Like many other websites, www.careerbless.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files may include internet protocol(IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp and other information about the use of this website, including a history of the pages you view. This does not contain any personally identifiable information. We use this information to improve our services.

* **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

www.careerbless.com uses cookies to personalise content and ads, to store information about visitors preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the users access or visit, to customize web page content based on visitors browser types, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

Some of the third-party vendors and ad networks use cookies on our site. www.careerbless.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party vendors and ad networks. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party vendors and ad networks for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.careerbless.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of the third-party vendors and ad networks

* **Google AdSense**

Third party vendors, including [Google](https://www.google.com/), use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to www.careerbless.com .

Google's use of the DoubleClick Cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the users based on their visit to www.careerbless.com and/or other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences). You can also visit [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

* **Google Analytics**

www.careerbless.com uses a tool called Google Analytics which uses cookies to collect information about how visitors use this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit, traffic sources etc. Google Analytics does not collect personally identifiable information. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to maintain and improve the website's technical performance. We do not (and do not allow any third party to) use Google Analytics to track, collect or upload any data that personally identifies an individual (such as a name, email address or billing information), or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information by Google. Please visit the page "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps" located at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) which explains how Google uses the data they collect.

Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of service, available at <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>, and the Google Privacy Policy, available at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy>

As a user you may opt out of the process Google Analytics uses to collect traffic log data. Google provides a browser add-on that enables users to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics, available at <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

* **Registration into www.careerbless.com**

This registration into this website permits the user to maintain and/or modify the data submitted to this website. This is an optional service provided by www.careerbless.com. Registration into www.careerbless.com requires that you supply certain personal information, including your full name, email, age and gender) to register. 

You may register or enhance your profile by linking your Google or Facebook or Twitter or Yahoo or LinkedIn account on www.careerbless.com. By doing this, you are asking them to send us certain information from those social media accounts, and you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use what they send us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You can unlink your social media accounts or control what they share from their privacy controls at any time.

When you sign in to www.careerbless.com through your Google or Facebook or Twitter or Yahoo or LinkedIn account, the respective service provider may set a cookie. For more details, please refer the privacy policies of the service providers(links are provided below)

The personal information which is collected during this registration process will not be distributed and shared with any third parties. While registering, you also agree to provide and maintain true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself. www.careerbless.com never verifies the accuracy of personal information that is submitted to this website, it is solely the responsibility of the user. www.careerbless.com reserves the right to suspend or permanently delete any user.

If you are under 18 years of age, then you must obtain your parent's or guardian's permission to register in this website.

For security measures, we record your IP address at the time of registration. This information is private.

* **Sharing Content through Social Media Platforms**

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate/engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

www.careerbless.com uses social media plugins provided by Google, Facebook and Twitter which helps to share web content directly from www.careerbless.com to the respective social media platform. When you share or recommend content through a social media platform, that action and any information you share will be covered by the privacy policy of the respective service provider. During this process, the service provider may set a cookie. For more details, please refer the privacy policies of the service providers (links are provided in section 6)

* **Youtube Plugin**

www.careerbless.com uses embedded YouTube video content which may use cookies. For more details, please refer [Google Privacy Policy.](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

* **User Generated Content and Public Activities**

We offer you opportunities to engage in public activities on www.careerbless.com. "Public activities" are any actions you take on www.careerbless.com that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, questions, answers, recommendations or any other items that you submit. Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name or ID, or any image or photo, becomes public and may be used by www.careerbless.com for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media. If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit can be read, collected and used by other users of these areas. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in the course of your public activities and we have no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or submissions. 

For security measures, we record your IP address when you perform any public activities on careerbless.com. This information is private.

* **Turning cookies off**

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

You can also visit [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising. For all other policies, please read our terms and conditions.
